Guide to the Frick Fine Arts Library Artist Files, 1892-1990 FFAL.002
ULS Frick Fine Arts Library
Frick Fine Arts Library Artist Files
1892-1990
1965-1985
ULS Frick Fine Arts Library
University of Pittsburgh. Department of Fine Arts
FFAL.002
20 Linear Feet
The Frick Fine Arts Library Artist Files contains numerous biographies, exhibition catalogs, announcements and more, that was collected by the library staff. Materials are primarily from the 1950s-1980s.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Scope and Content Notes
The Frick Fine Arts Library Artist Files contains numerous biographies, exhibition catalogs, and announcements, such as posters, postcards, and letters mailed to the library. Additional ephemera includes newspaper clippings and magazine articles. Notable items are indicated at the folder level.
Related Material
Frick Fine Arts Library Subject Files, 1939-1989, FFAL.001, Frick Fine Arts Library, University of Pittsburgh
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in its original order as maintained by the Frick Fine Arts Library. Some shifting of materials was done in order to place artists according to the Library of Congress Name Authority File. Series 1 contains folders of artists grouped alphabetically by last name. Series 2 consists of folders devoted to individual artists.
History
The Frick Fine Arts Library collected materials relating to individual artists in the Pittsburgh region, nationally, and some internationally. The majority of the materials were amassed after the library moved from the Cathedral of Learning to the new Frick Fine Arts Building in 1965.
Exhibition catalogs; University of Pittsburgh; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Art -- Library resources; Art -- 20th century; Frick Fine Arts Library
- Multiple Artist Files, I.; 259 folders
  Scope and Content Notes
  Artist files arranged in alphabetical groupings.
  - American Artists (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 1)
    Biographies of American West artists and reproductions of works.
    Blake, Buckeye, 1946-; Blaylock, Ted; Bryers, Duane; Carter, Gary; Christie, Keith; Crook, Don; De Mille, Leslie B. (Leslie Benjamin), 1927-; DiVita, Frank; Emmons, Glenn E.; Fraughton, Edward J. 1938-; Goebel, Rod; Goodacre, G. (Glenna); Greeves, R. V. (Richard V.); Hampton, John W. (John Wade), 1918-2000; Heikka, Earle Erik; Hines, Jack, 1923-; Houston, Cody; Janoff, Larry; Kapp, Gary; Lorimer, Lisa Danielle; Lorimer, Thomas W.; Overstreet, Anne Aller; Reese, William; Remington, Frederic, 1861-1909; Schelling, George Luther; Schwiering, Conrad, 1916-; Smith, Lowell Ellsworth, 1924-2008; Speed, Grant, 1930-2011; Teague, Donald, 1897-; Velazques, Joseph E.; Williford, Hollis; Zemsky, JessicaAbbe, Elfriede, 1919-2012; Abbema, Louise, 1858-1927; Abbott, Yarnall; Abeles, Sigmund, 1934-; Abish, Cecile; Abney, Odelle; Abranches Townsend, Helena Dunshee de; Abularach, Rodolfo, 1933-; Accardi, Carla; Acconci, Vito, 1940-
  - A-Ac (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 2)
    Abbe, Elfriede, 1919-2012; Abbema, Louise, 1858-1927; Abbott, Yarnall; Abeles, Sigmund, 1934-; Abish, Cecile; Abney, Odelle; Abranches Townsend, Helena Dunshee de; Abularach, Rodolfo, 1933-; Accardi, Carla; Acconci, Vito, 1940-
  - Ad (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 3)
    Adair, Maria; Adam, Henri-Georges, 1904-1967; Adams, Alice, 1930-; Adams, Ansel, 1902-1984; Adams, Clinton, 1918-2002; Adams, Helen Coolidge; Adams, Herbert; Adams, Pat, 1928-; Adams, Robert, 1937-; Adler, Jankel, 1895-1949; Adler, Lee, 1934-
  - Af-Ai (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 4)
    Africano, Nicholas, 1948-; Agam, Yaacov, 1928-; Agostini, Peter; Agostini, Sergio; Aguilar, Mauricio, 1919-; Ahlgren, Roy B., 1927-; Ahmad, Sufi; Aidlin, Jerry; Airola, Paavo; Aitchison, Craigie, 1926-2009
  - Aj-Ald (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 5)
    Ajay, Abe; Alber, Rose; Albers, Anni; Albright, Ivan; Alcosser, Murray, 1937-; Aldaraca, Amado
  - Ale (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 6)
    Alechinsky, Pierre, 1927-; Lisboa, Antônio Francisco, 1730?-1814; Alexander, John, 1945-; Alexander, John White, 1856-1915; Alexandre, Francesca
  - Ali-Alv (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 7)
    Ali, Ron; Alicante, Mary; Allen, Douglas, 1935-; Allongé, Auguste, 1833-1898; Alps, Glen; Alten, Mathian Joseph; Altman, Harold, 1924-2003; Altoon, John, 1925-1969; Alvarado-Juárez, Francisco, 1950-
  - Am-And (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 8)
    Aman, Theodor, 1831-1891; Amaro, Mario Pariente; Amarotico, Joseph Anthony, 1931-1986; Amateis, Edmond Romulus, 1897-1981; Amenoff, Gregory, 1948-; Amino, Leo, 1911-1989; Andersen, Leif; Anderson, Eileen; Anderson, John; Andrade, Edna, 1917-; Andreescu, Ion, 1850-1882; Andres, Maria Helena, 1922-; Andrews, Benny, 1930-2006; Andrews, Michael, 1928-1995; Andrews, Oliver, 1925-1978; Andriulli, Carol; Andriulli, Robert
  - Ane-Arm (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 9)
    Ángel, Félix; Angeli, Franco, 1935-1988; Anliker, Roger (Roger William), 1924-; Anselmo, Giovanni, 1934-; Anshutz, Thomas Pollock 1851-1912; Antes, Horst, 1936-; Anuszkiewicz, Richard; Apostolides, Zoe, 1927-; Appel, Eric; Appel, Karel, 1921-2006; Applebroog, Ida; Appleby, Jean E.; Aquino, Edmundo; Aquino, Humberto, 1947-; Arakawa, Shusaku, 1936-2010; Archipenko, Alexander, 1887-1964; Ardissone, Yolande, 1927-; Arikha, Avigdor, 1929-2010; Armajani, Siah, 1939-; Arman, 1928-2005; Armstrong, David; Armstrong, Jane B.; Armstrong, Martha, 1940-
  - Arn-As (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 10)
    Arentz, Dick; Arnal, Enrique, 1932-; Arnal, Jean, 1907-1987; Arneson, Robert, 1930-1992; Arnest, Bernard, 1917-1986; Arnold-Kayser, Bernita, 1911-; Arnoldi, Charles, 1946-; Aronson, Carol Lena, 1941-; Arp, Jean, 1887-1966; Arp, Jean, 1887-1966; Arranz, Lorenzo, 1930-; Asawa, Ruth; Ascher, Daisy, 1944-; Aschkenas, David, 1951-; Ashbaugh, Dennis, 1946-; Asher, Elise1914-; Asplund, Tore, 1903-1978
  - At-Av (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 11)
    Includes John James Audubon exhibition catalog: "John James Audubon: The Man, and His Achievement," Kennedy Galleries, Inc., New York, undated.
    Atget, Eugene, 1857-1927; Atkins, Jerry, 1939-; Aubert, Jean Ernest, 1824-1906; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851; Auerbach, Frank, 1931-; Augé, Philippe, 1935-; Auld, Albert Michael, 1943-; Ault, George, 1891-1948; Austin, Darrel, 1907-1994; Autio, Rudy, 1926-2007; Avati, Mario, 1921-; Avedisian, Edward, 1936-2007; Aviles, San, 1932-1991
  - Aw-Az (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 12)
    Ay-O, 1931-; Ayrton, Michael, 1921-1975; Azar, Aquiles, 1932-
  - Ba-Bad (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 13)
    Babarović, Ivo; Babb, Larry R.; Baber, Alice; Bach, Dirk, 1961-2012; Bacon, Francis, 1909-1992; Bacon, Nancy, 1940-; Bacon, Peggy, 1895-1987
  - Bae-Ban (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 14)
    Baer, George, 1895-1971; Baer, Martin, 1895-1961; Bahautdin, Rem; Baizerman, Saul, 1889-1957; Bak, Samuel; Baker, Lamar, 1908-1994; Baker, Lawrence, 1930-; Baker, Roger, 1925-; Bakst, Léon, 1866-1924; Baldinger, Louise; Baldwin, Douglas; Ball, Julia; Balsley, John; Bancila, Octav, 1872-1944; Bank, Arnold; Banks, Virginia, 1920-1985; Bannard, Walter Darby, 1934-
  - Bao-Barr (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 15)
    Barbash, Steven, 1933-; Barber, John; Barborini, Bruno; Barcala, Washington, 1920-1993; Bargheer, Eduard, 1901-1979; Barie, Judy; Barill, Mark A.; Barkley, Vernon; Barlach, Ernst, 1870-1938; Barnet, Will, 1911-2012; Barnett, Herbert, 1910-1972; Barney, Alice, 1857-1931; Barr, David, 1939-; Barreda, Ernesto, 1927-; Barrera, Antonio, 1948-1990; Barrias, Felix Joseph, 1822-1907; Barzboa, Carlos
  - Bars-Baz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 16)
    Bartels, Hermann, 1928-1989; Bartle, Annette; Bartlett, Clay, 1907-1955; Bartlett, Jennifer, 1941-; Barton, Loren, 1893-1975; Barye, Antoine Louis, 1796-1875; Basaldella, Mirko, 1910-1969; Bates, JoAnne W.; Bates, Leo; Bates, Wayne L.; Batista, Kenneth; Battke, Heinz, 1900-1966; Bauder, Tammy; Bauer, Molly; Bauer, Rudolf, 1889-1953; Baugh, Thomas; Baum, Mark, 1903-1997; Baumgarten, Lothar; Baumol, William J.; Bayer, Herbert, 1900-1985; Baylinson, Abraham; Baynard, Ed, 1940-; Baziotes, William, 1912-1963
  - Bb-Bea (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 17)
    Beach, Chester, 1881-1956; Beal, Gifford, 1879-1956; Beaman, Richard B.; Bearden, Romare, 1911-1988; Beardman, John; Beardsley, Aubrey, 1872-1898; Beasley, Bruce, 1939-; Beauchamp, Robert, 1923-1995; Beaudin, André, 1895-1979; Beaumont, Elie de
  - Bea-Bel (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 18)
    Bechtol, Robert; Beck, Margit, 1915-1997; Beckley, Jon; Bedel, Walter; Beggs, Edward; Behl, Wolfgang; Behrens, Howard, 1933-; Beittel, Kenneth R.; Béjar, Feliciano; Belain, Fernando; Belaunzaran, Carlos; Bell, Charles, 1935-; Belle, Cecile; Bellon, George Paul; Bellows, George, 1882-1925
  - Bem-Ben (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 19)
    Ben-Haim, Ammon; Ben-Haim, Zigi, 1945-; Bender, John; Bender, Whitney; Bendersky, Jaime, 1922-1997; Bengochea, Miguel Angel, 1945-; Bengston, Billy Al; Benjamin, Anthony, 1931-; Benn, Ben, 1884-; Bennett, Rainey; Bennett, Ron; Benson, Frank Weston, 1862-1951; Bentley, Claude Ronald, 1915-1990; Beny, Roloff
  - Beo-Ber (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 20)
    Béraud, Jean, 1849-1935; Berdich, Vera, 1915-2003; Berend-Corinth, Charlotte, 1880-1967; Berg, Peter, 1948-; Berge, Dorothy; Berhang, Mattie; Berkowitz, Leon, 1919-1987; Berman, Becky; Berman, Eugene, 1899-1972; Berman, Saul; Berman, Steve; Berman, Wallace, 1926-1976; Bermúdez, José; Bermúdez, Lía, 1930-; Bernardo, Mane; Bernini, Gian Lorenzo, 1598-1680; Bernstein, Barbara; Bernstein, Judith; Berresford, Virginia; Bertier, Francisque Edouard; Bertrand, Gaston, 1910-1994
  - Bes-Bez (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 21)
    Besnard, Paul Albert, 1849-1934; Bessemer, Auriel; Besser, Arne; Beteta, Ignacio M.; Betsberg, Ernestine; Betts, Edward H., 1920-2008
  - Bf-Bil (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 22)
    Bhavsar, Natvar, 1934-; Biala, Janice, 1904-2000; Biddle, George, 1885-1973; Bidó, Cándido, 1936-; Bienfait, Aline, 1941-; Bierge, Roland; Bierstadt, Albert, 1830-1902; Bigatti, Alfredo, 1898-1964; Biggs, Janet, 1959-; Bill, Jakob; Bill, Max, 1908-1994; Billings, Henry, 1901-
  - Bim-Bla (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 23)
    Binai, Paul; Bineck, Rainer; Birmelin, Robert, 1933-; Birolli, Renato, 1905?-1959; Bishop, Isabel, 1902-1988; Bishop, Richard E. (Richard Evett), 1887-1975; Bissel, Ann Angel; Bissière, Roger, 1886-1964; Bisti, Dmitri; Blackburn, Morris, 1902-1979; Blackwell, Tom, 1938-; Blagden, Allen, 1938-; Blagovolin, N. S. (Nikolaĭ Stepanovich); Blaine, Nell, 1922-1996; Blair, Barbara; Blakelock, Ralph A, 1947-1919.; Blanchard, Carol
  - Ble-Bly (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 24)
    Bleckner, Ross; Bledsoe, Judith; Blessing, Charles A.; Blizzard, Alan; Bloch, Albert; Blodgett, Peter J. (Peter John), 1954-; Bluemner, Oscar, 1867-1938; Blum, Robert Frederick, 1857-1903.; Blum, Zevi; Blume, Peter, 1906-1992; Blumenfeld, Rochelle; Blythe, David Gilmour, 1815-1865
  - Bm-Bog (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 25)
    Bobick, Bruce; Bobri, Vladimir; Bodin, Paul, 1910-1994; Bodnar, Peter; Boeckl, Herbert, 1894-1966; Beltrán Bofill, Joan; Boggs, Frank, 1955-1926; Boghosian, Varujan; Bogue-Overbay, Paula
  - Boh-Bone (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 26)
    Bolin, Gustav, 1920-; Bolliger, Hans, 1915-; Bolotowsky, Ilya, 1907-1981; Bolshakova, Irina; Bona, 1926-2000; Bonacker, Joyce; Bone, Muirhead, Sir, 1876-1953; Bonevardi, Marcelo, 1929-1994
  - Bonf-Bonz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 27)
    Bonfanti, Arturo, 1905-1978; Bonheur, Rosa, 1822-1899; Bonhomme, Léon, 1870-1924; Bonington, Richard Parkes, 1801-1828; Bonnard, Pierre, 1867-1947; Bonnat, Léon Joseph Florentin, 1833-1922; Bonnefoy, Henri-Arthur; Bonomi, Maria, 1935-; Bonvin, Francois, 1817-1887
  - Boo-Bot (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 28)
    Bookbinder, Jack, 1911-1990; Booth, Robert; Bordas, Edward; Borduas, Paul-Emile, 1905-1960; Borglum, Gutzon, 1867-1941; Bornstein, Eli; Borodin, Anatoly; Borofsky, Jonathan, 1942-; Bos, Lindsay; Botero, Fernando, 1932-; Botkin, Henry Albert, 1896-1983; Bottinelli, Constance; Botton, Jean de, 1898-1978
  - Bou-Boz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 29)
    Bouché, Louis, 1896-1969; Boucher, François, 1703-1770; Bougher, George; Bouguereau, William Adolphe, 1825-1905; Boulanger, Gustave, 1824-1888; Bourdelle, Antoine, 1861-1929; Bourgeois, Louise 1911-2010; Bourke-White, Margaret, 1904-1971; Bourrie, Andre 1936-; Bovard, Ronald; Boxer, David 1946-; Boxer, Stanley; Boyce, Gerald E., 1933-; Boyle, Keith 1930-; Boynton, James, 1928-2010
  - Bp-Braq (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 30)
    Includes exhibition catalog: "The Sculpture of Georges Braque," The Contemporary Arts Center, Cincinnati Art Museum, 1956-1957.
    Brach, Paul, 1924-2007; Bradley, Peter, 1940-; Brady, Carolyn; Brady, Mathew B., approximately 1823-1896; Bragg, Charles; Brainard, Joe, 1942-1994; Brakke, Mike; Bramgwyn, Frank; Bramson, Phyllis; Brandt, Sérgio Alberto; Brandt, Bill; Brandt, Warren, 1918-2002; Braque, Georges, 1882-1963; Brasher, Rex, 1869-1960; Brauner, Victor, 1903-1966
  - Brar-Bre (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 31)
    Brasilier, Andre, 1929-; Bratby, John, 1928-1992; Brauner, Victor, 1903-1966; Braux, Rene de; Breer, Robert; Breetvelt, Dolf, 1892-1975; Brejcha, Vernon, 1942-; Brenson, Theodore, 1893-1959; Breu, Jörg, approximately 1480-1537
  - Brf-Brod (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 32)
    Brianchon, Maurice, 1899-1979; Brice, William, 1921-2008; Brisson, Jean; Brittain, Miller Gore, 1912-1968; Britton, James, 1878-1936; Brockhurst, Gerald Leslie, 1890-1978; Broderson, Morris, 1928-2011; Broderson, Robert; Brodie, Regis C.
  - Broe-Broz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 33)
    Brokaw, Lucile; Broman, Shirley; Broodthaers, Marcel; Brook, Alexander, 1898-1980; Brooker, Moe; Brooks, Leonard, 1911-2011; Brorby, Harry; Brouwn, Stanley; Brown, Augustus C. Jr.; Brown, Aurelia; Brown, Carlyle; Brown, David; Brown, Everald, 1917-2002; Brown, Gary H.; Brown, Hilton, 1938-; Brown, Joan, 1938-1990; Brown, Judith S., 1931-1992; Brown, Kenneth S.; Brown, Malcolm, 1931-; Brown, Roger, 1941-1997; Brown, William Theo, 1919-; Browne, Byron, 1907-1961; Browne, Martha; Browning, Colleen
  - Bru-Bul (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 34)
    Bru, Salvador; Dramard, Georges de; Draper, William F., 1912-2003; Drescher, Ruth; Drewes, Werner, 1899-1985; Drexel, (Hans) Christof, 1886-1979; Drexler, Sherman; Drisch, Russell; Driskell, David, 1963-; Drudis, Jose; Drum, Sydney; Dubin, Ralph; DuBois, Guy Pene; Dubuffe, Guillame; Duca, Alfred M.; Dudchenko, Boris; Dudchenko, NancyBruck, Lajos; Brunken, Glen; Brush, George de Forest, 1855-1941; Brush, Gloria DeFilipps; Bruya, Marilyn; Bruya, Robert; Bryan, Pamela; Bub, Ray; Bubb, John Abram; Buday, Gene; Buffet, Bernard, 1928-1999; Buggiani, Paolo; Bull, Fran, 1938-; Bultman, Fritz, 1919-1985
  - Bum-Burk (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 35)
    Bunce, Louis, 1907-1983; Buonagurio, Toby, 1947-; Burchard, Pablo; Burchfield, Charles, 1893-1967; Burden, Chris, 1946-2015; Burford, Robert, 1791-1861; Burgin, Victor; Burke, Ainslie, 1922-; Burke, Bill, 1943-; Burke, Selma, 1900-1995; Burko, Diane, 1945-
  - Burl-Burz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 36)
    Burle Marx, Roberto, 1909-1994; Burlin, Paul, 1886-1969; Burliuk, David, 1882-1967; Burns, Mark, 1950-; Burri, Alberto, 1915-1995; Bursztynowicz, Henry; Burton, Hubert, -1940; Bury, Claus, 1946-; Bury, Rol
  - Bus-Bz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 37)
    Busa, Peter, 1914-1985; Bush, Jack, 1909-1977; Butler, Reg, 1913-1981; Butler, Theodore Earl, 1861-1936; Buttersworth, James Edward, 1817-1894.; Buzzelli, Joseph; Byrne, James
  - Caa-Cae (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 38)
    Cabanel, Alexandre, 1823-1889; Cabrera, Miguel, 1695-1768; Cabrera, Roberto, 1939-; Cabrera Moreno, Servando, 1923-1981; Cadmus, Paul, 1904-1999; Cadoret, Michel, 1912-1985; Caesar, Doris, 1893-1971; Lassalle, C. (Camille) also known as Camille-Léopold Cabaillot-Lassalle
  - Caf-Calc (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 39)
    Caffrey, Dennis, 1946-; Cagan, Steve, 1943-; Cagli, Corrado, 1910-1976; Cain, Georges, 1856-1919; Cairns, Kathleen H.; Cajori, Charles, 1921-2013; Calaboyias, Peter, 1940-; Calabria, Ennio,1937-; Calcagno, Lawrence, 1913-1993
  - Cald-Calz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 40)
    Calder, Alexander Stirling, 1870-1945; Calderara, Antonio, 1903-1978; Calderón, Coqui, 1937-; Caldwell, William V.; Callahan, Kenneth, 1905-1986; Callery, Mary, 1903-1977; Callot, Jacques, 1592-1635; Calpena, Vicente Pastor
  - Cam-Can (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 41)
    Camacho, Jorge Alejandro, 1964-; Camargo, Ibere, 1914-1994; Cameron, Eric, 1935-; Camp, Jeffery; Campbell, Charles, 1905-1985; Campbell, George, 1917-; Campbell, Jim, 1956-; Campbell, Kenneth; Campbell, Michael; Campbell, Nancy; Campbell, Orland, 1890-1972; Campbell, Metson, and Brown; Cañas, Carlos, 1924-; Canavesio, Giovanni, active 1450-1500; Candell, Victor, 1903-1977; Candhales, Rodriguez; Canfield, Jane White; Canogar, Rafael, 1935-; Cantú, Federico, 1908-1989
  - Cao-Carl (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 42)
    Capa, Robert, 1913-1954; Caplan, Gerald L.; Caponigro, Paul, 1932-; Capristo, Oscar; Capron, Jean; Carballo, Aída, 1916-; Cardano, Clelia; Cárdenas, René; Cardinale, Helene; Careaga, Enrique; Carles, Arthur B., 1882-1952; Carlson, Cynthia, 1942-
  - Carm-Carr (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 43)
    Caro, Anthony, 1924-2013; Caro, Bill; Carpenter, Gilbert F.; Carpentier, Evariste; Carreño, Mario; Carrington, Leonora, 1917-2011; Carroll, Maryrose
  - Cars-Cas (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 44)
    Carter, Bruce, 1930-; Carter, Clarence Holbrook, 1904-2000; Carter, Stevens; Carter-Smyth, George; Cartmell, Robert, 1939-; Carton, Norman; Caruso, Nino; Carvalho, Luiz Woods de; Carybe, 1911-1997; Casanova, Francesco Giuseppe, approximately 1732-1803; Casanova, Teresa; Casaus, Jesús, 1926-; Cascella, Michele, 1892-1989; Casebier, Cecil Lang; Caspari, Claus, 1911-; Cassatt, Mary, 1844-1926; Cassigneul, Jean-Pierre; Castel, Moshe Elazar, 1909-1992; Castellón, Federico, 1914-1971; Castellón, Rolando; Castillo, Sergio; Castle, Wendell, 1932-; Castrocid, Enrique
  - Cat-Cd (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1)
    Cathelin, Bernard; Cato, Bob; Caulfield, Patrick, 1936-2005; Cauvel, Robert; Cavael, Rolf, 1898-1979; Cavaillès, Jules, 1901-1977; Cavallaro, Vincent; Cavallon, Giorgio, 1904-1989; Cazin, Jean Charles, 1841-1901
  - Ce-Chad (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 46)
    Includes Cezanne exhibition catalog, "A Loan Exhibition of Cezanne for the Benefit of the New York Infirmary" at Wildenstein March 27-April 26, 1947, New York; reproductions of five Cezanne paintings: "Fleurs dans un vase," "Nature morte au pichet," "Le jeune homme au petit chapeau," "Tournant de route a Auvers," "Portrait de Madame Cezanne en rouge," along with provenance and exhibiton information through 1928.
    Cecere, Gaetano, 1894-1985; Celender, Don, 1931-2005; Ceroli, Mario; Cezanne, Paul, 1839-1906; Chab, Victor, 1930-; Chadbourn, Alfred
  - Chai-Chap (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 47)
    Chaiken, William E.; Chailloux, Roger, 1931-1977; Chakrian, Hagop; Chalfant, Henry; Chalker-Tennant, Nancy; Chamberlain, Samuel, 1895-1975; Chambers, Thomas, 1808-1869; Chan, Henri; Chaney, James; Changnon, Michael; Chann, George, 1913-; Channin, Richard; Chapa, Martha, 1946-; Chapin, David, 1939-; Chapin, James, 1887-1975
  - Char-Chen (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 48)
    Charles, Peter, 1943-; Charley, Alfred, 1936-; Charlot, Jean, 1898-1979; Charman, Jessie Bone1895-; Charman, Fredrick Montague; Charon, Guy; Charoy, Bernard; Chauffrey, Jean; Chellew, Gabriela; Chemeche, George, 1934-; Chen, Chi, 1912-; Chen, Hilo; Chen, Komi
  - Cheo-Chiz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 49)
    Cheret, Jules, 1836-1932; Cherney, Marvin, 1925-1967; Chernoff, Florence B.; Chesley, Jacqueline; Chesney, Lee (the elder); Chesney, Lee, 1920-; Chevolleau, Jean, 1924-; Chicago, Judy, 1939-; Chihuly, Dale, 1941-; Child, Charles; Chillida, Eduardo, 1924-2002; Chimkevitch, Sacha, 1920-; Chinas, Joaquin; Chinmoy, Sri, 1931-2007; Chinni, Peter; Chiriacka, Ernest, 1913-2010; De Chirico, Giorgio, 1888-1978; Chittock, Derek; Chiu, Teng Hiok, 1903-1972
  - Chj-Ciz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 50)
    Includes Christo "Valley Curtain, Rifle, Colorado" Documentation booklet. The Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, 1971.
    Chotiner, Robert; Zhou, Jianxiong; Christensen, Dan, 1942-2007; Christo, 1935-; Christ-Janer, Albert, 1910-1973; Chrystie, E. P.; Cicero, Carmen, 1926-; Citron, Minna, 1896-1991; Civitello, John, 1939-
  - Cj-Cl (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 51)
    Clancy, Tom; Clark, Allan, 1896-1950; Clark, Elizabeth; Clark, Grace R.; Clark, Larry; Clark, Roland, 1874-1957; Clarke, Allan Hugh; Clay, Vaughn; Clays, Paul-Jean, 1819-1900; Clergue, Lucien; Clerk, Pierre, 1928-; Clermont-Gallerande, Adhemar Louis; Cloar, Carroll; Clutz, William
  - Coa-Com (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 52)
    Coburn, Alvin Langdon, 1882-1966; Cockburn, Patricia, 1914-1989; Cohen Gan, Pinchas; Cohen, Becky; Cohen, Harold, 1928-2016; Cohoon, Hannah, 1788-1864; Coiner, Charles T., 1898-1989; Coke, Van Deren, 1921-2004; Colarusso, Jim; Cole, Bernard; Cole, Thomas, 1801-1848; Coleman, Glenn O., 1887-1932; Coleman, Michael, 1946 June 25-; Colescott, Warrington, 1921-; Collie, Alberto; Collins, Joel (Joel R.); Collins, Pat; Collins, Robert; Collins, Thom; Colt, John N.; Colville, Alex, 1920-2013; Comerre, Léon, 1850-1916; Comerre-Paton, Jacqueline
  - Con-Cori (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 1, Folder 53)
    Conner, Bruce, 1933-2008; Conrow, Wilford Seymour; Benjamin-Constant, 1845-1902; Constantine, Greg, 1938-; Consuegra, Hugo, 1929-; Conte, Michelangelo, 1913-; Contino, Leonard; Contis, Peter; Cook, Robert H.; Cook, Robert, 1921-; Cooley, Cynthia F.; Cooper, Ruffin; Copley, John Singleton, 1738-1815; Coppock, Donovan; Corbett, Tish; Corbino, Jon, 1905-1964; Córdova, Inés; Corinth, Lovis, 1858-1925
  - Corj-Cou (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 54)
    Cornelius, Marty; Cornelius, Robert C.; Cornell, Joseph, 1903-1972; Coronel, Rafael, 1932-; Corot, Jean-Baptiste-Camille, 1796-1875; Corpora, Antonio, 1909-2004; Correggio, 1489?-1534; Corsini, Harold; Cosindas, Marie; Cot, Pierre-Auguste, 1837-1883; Cottrell, Kenneth; Coughlin, Jack; Coughlin, Mildred, 1892-1984; Counts, Charles; Courbet, Gustave, 1819-1877; Courtin, Pierre, 1921-
  - Cov-Cre (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 55)
    Includes six prints signed and numbered by Lee Brown Coye.
    Cowans, Adger; Cowgill, Molly; Cowles, Russell, 1887-1979; Cox, Jan, 1919-1980; Cox, Valda; Coye, Lee Brown, 1907-1981; Coyle, Carolyn; Cramer, Konrad, 1888-1963; Cramer, Richard, 1932-; Crawford, Ralston, 1906-1978; Creamer, George; Cremean, Robert, 1932-; Cremonini, Leonardo, 1925-2010; Cretara, Dominic
  - Cri-Cur (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 56)
    Crile, Susan, 1942-; Crodel, Charles, 1894-1973; Cronin, Robert, 1936-; Cross, Tom, 1931-2009; Crotti, Jean, 1878-1958; Crow, Nancy, 1943-; Cruxent, José María.; Cuevas, José Luis, 1934-; Culver, Charles B. (Charles Beach), 1908-1967; Cumming, Diana; Cunliffe, Mitzi Solomon, 1918-; Cunliffe, Peter; Cunningham, Imogen, 1883-1976; Curry, John Steuart, 1897-1946; Curtis, Leland
  - Cus-Cz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 57)
    Cusimano, Joseph, 1935-; Cuthbert, Virginia, 1908-2001; Cutler, Charles Gordon, 1914-; Cuyp, Aelbert, 1620-1691; Cyril; Czeschka, Carl Otto, 1878-1960
  - Daa-Dar (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 58)
    D'Arcangelo, Allan, 1930-1998; Dabo, Leon, 1868-1960; Dahlgreen, Charles W. (Charles William), 1864-1955; Daley, William, 1925-; Damiani, Jorge, 1931-; Daniels, Elizabeth Strandt; Daphnis, Nassos, 1914-2010; Daraniyagala, Justin, 1903-1967; Darboven, Hanne
  - Das-Dau (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 59)